let savollar6 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to alert",
      answer: "C. ogohlantirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
        "B. unutmoq",
        "C. ogohlantirmoq",
        "D. yashirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "broadcast",
      answer: "A. ko'rsatuv",
      options: [
        "A. ko'rsatuv",
        "B. reklama",
        "C. e'lon",
        "D. jurnal"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "bulletin",
      answer: "D. yangiliklar",
      options: [
        "A. intervyu",
        "B. reklama",
        "C. hujjatli film",
        "D. yangiliklar"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "bump",
      answer: "B. ishik",
      options: [
        "A. jaroxat",
        "B. ishik",
        "C. chandiq",
        "D. yara"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to chop",
      answer: "C. to'g'ramoq",
      options: [
        "A. kesmoq",
        "B. qirqmoq",
        "C. to'g'ramoq",
        "D. to'g'ramoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "closet",
      answer: "A. shkaf",
      options: [
        "A. shkaf",
        "B. javon",
        "C. sandiq",
        "D. tokcha"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "to console",
      answer: "D. yupatmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tergamoq",
        "B. koyimoq",
        "C. qo'rqitmoq",
        "D. yupatmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "district",
      answer: "B. tuman",
      options: [
        "A. shahar",
        "B. tuman",
        "C. viloyat",
        "D. davlat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "drawer",
      answer: "C. tortma",
      options: [
        "A. tokcha",
        "B. quti",
        "C. tortma",
        "D. javon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to endure",
      answer: "A. chidamoq",
      options: [
        "A. chidamoq",
        "B. qochmoq",
        "C. yashirmoq",
        "D. qutulmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "to execute",
      answer: "B. qatl qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. hibsga olmoq",
        "B. qatl qilmoq",
        "C. hukm qilmoq",
        "D. jazolamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to grasp",
      answer: "C. ushlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. qo'yib yubormoq",
        "B. tashlamoq",
        "C. ushlamoq",
        "D. silkitmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "rear",
      answer: "D. orqa tomon",
      options: [
        "A. old tomon",
        "B. yon tomon",
        "C. yuqori tomon",
        "D. orqa tomon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "senator",
      answer: "A. senator",
      options: [
        "A. senator",
        "B. vazir",
        "C. sudya",
        "D. elchi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "skull",
      answer: "B. bosh suyagi",
      options: [
        "A. umurtqa",
        "B. bosh suyagi",
        "C. qovurg'a",
        "D. suyak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to stir",
      answer: "C. aralashtirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. silkitmoq",
        "B. qormoq",
        "C. aralashtirmoq",
        "D. ezmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to tap",
      answer: "A. bosmoq",
      options: [
        "A. bosmoq",
        "B. bosmoq",
        "C. turtmoq",
        "D. qattiq urmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "tremendous",
      answer: "D. ulkan",
      options: [
        "A. kichik",
        "B. o'rtacha",
        "C. normal",
        "D. ulkan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "underneath",
      answer: "B. ostida",
      options: [
        "A. ustida",
        "B. ostida",
        "C. yonida",
        "D. orasida"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "worm",
      answer: "C. chuvalchang",
      options: [
        "A. ilon",
        "B. qurt",
        "C. chuvalchang",
        "D. qo'ng'iz"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
export default savollar6;